I don't know if y'all do this, but I'm going to ask you to envision a future for yourself.
So often we don't do this because we have limitations that are right here and present that impede us from doing so.
However, I want you to move past those impediments, those obstacles, as real as they are.
Just imagine they're not there.
And envision a future for yourself.
I want you to envision this future for yourself as honestly and as purely as possible.
I want you to see the path before you.
I want you to see the ways in which you may have been impeded from being on that path, but were there no impediments whatsoever, what path would you take?
I want you to do this because the future for yourself is so often the inspiration that you need.
To imagine a future for all of us.
And seeing a future that exists is so often the catalyst for the courage you need to step into purpose in a way that you never have before.
And what we need now is people stepping out of fear and stepping into their imagination so that they can turn dreams into goals, into plans.
And in order to do that, you first got to envision it so you can take the step toward it.
Support a real one.